<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Music Place</string>

    <!-- Menu item name for my music [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="menu_my_music">My Music</string>

    <!-- Menu item name for buy music [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="menu_buy_music">Buy Music</string>

    <!-- Menu item name for now playing [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="menu_now_playing">Now Playing</string>

    <!-- My Music activity screen explanation -->
    <string name="my_music_details">
        This screen will have 3 clickable TextViews for Recent Playlists, All playlists and All Songs.\n\n
        On clicking these activities, it will start corresponding activity and show a new screen. Recent Playlists activity will
        show list of all playlists played in the last 1 week. All playlists activity will show list of all the user playlists.
        All songs activity will show list of all songs.\n\n
        This screen will also have a button to create a new playlist.On clicking this button, the user will be able to create
        new playlist from the existing songs from songs library.
    </string>

    <!-- Buy Music activity screen explanation -->
    <string name="buy_music_details">
        This screen will have 1 clickable TextView for buying songs from Google Play Music store.\n\n
        On clicking this TextView, it will open either Google Play Music app on the device or browse
        to the music store on Google Play Store website. The user can then buy music from the play music store.\n\n
        First the app will try to open the Google Play Music app if it is installed on the device using:\n\n
        Intent intent = context.getPackageManager().getLaunchIntentForPackage("com.google.android.music");
        startActivity(intent);\n\n
        If the app is not installed, browse to the Google Play Music website to buy music using:\n\n
        startActivity(new Intent(Intent.ACTION_VIEW, Uri.parse("https://play.google.com/store/music")));
    </string>

    <!-- Now Playing activity screen explanation -->
    <string name="now_paying_details">
        This screen will have an image that shows the poster of the album or movie the song is from.\n\n
        Below the image, it will show couple of words representing the song. Below that it will show the singer name.\n\n
        Below that, it will have time bar that will show the progress as the song is played.\n\n
        Below that it will have buttons to play or pause, forward to next song and go back to previous song.
    </string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
</resources>
